dipdive.com 2017-12-14

# will.i.am - privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information, including your personal information on the interactive Service operated and controlled by i.am.bizzy, llc a legal entity based in the United States including, but not limited to, the Website currently located at [www.i.am](http://www.i.am/) and [http://will.i.am](http://will.i.am/) (the " **Site** "), and any applications, interactive features, widgets and resources that may be offered by will.i.am through Internet Web sites, mobile devices or other platforms (all of which, together with the Site, are collectively referred to as the “ **will.i.am website** ” or “ **Website** ”). i.am.bizzy operates the Website on behalf of itself and its affiliated companies (“ **Affiliates** ”).

Please read through carefully to understand our practices regarding personal information and how we use and treat it.

**MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION PREFERENCES**

We will not disclose Personal Data (as defined below) to third parties, including for their direct marketing purposes, without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. If, after providing consent, you want to opt out of having your Personal Data disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please let us know by sending us an email at [privacy@i.am](mailto:privacy@i.am)

You have the right to ask us not to process your Personal Data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us at [privacy@i.am](mailto:privacy@i.am).

In each instance, please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically state that you do not want your Personal Data shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and/or whether you object to us using your data for marketing purposes.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Personal Data**

We may collect and process information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you, (e.g., your name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number or other identifiers (“ **Personal Data** ”). We request Personal Data from you when you register on the Service. In addition to information collected during registration, we may collect Personal Data that you voluntarily provide, for example, in e-mails to our Service, in information shared or posted using the Service's functionality, as well as online order and registration forms and surveys or when you make use of the Services or make purchases via our Service.

Please note that the information which we may process and collect may include information or identities which are included within materials or content posted by you via our Services. You should consider whether it is appropriate to post such material or content but also whether any other person may be identified from such material or content. You are responsible for ensuring you have the consent of any individual who personal information or details can be identified from your postings. If in doubt check with the individual concerned. Remember a photo or image can be personal information and identify another person.

Some Personal Data we request may be optional. If you choose to withhold certain requested information, however, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site or Service.

In addition to the Personal Data set out above we may collect additional information, including:

  * details of your visits to any of our Sites(s) including, but not limited to, traffic data, general location data (for example you are in a particular country, region or state), weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access; and
  * your third party social network credentials when you opt to link those accounts to i.am.bizzy

**Nonpersonal Data**

In addition to Personal Data, we may collect and/or track information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, (e.g., demographic information (like age, profession or gender), domain names, certain IP addresses, information about the device or any computer you may use to download or stream a copy of our app or Service onto your device, including, where available, the device's or computer's unique device identifiers, operating system, browser type and mobile network information, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), clickstream data, browser type and language, viewed and exit pages and date or time stamps and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Service (“ **Nonpersonal Data** ”).

We may share such information with select Third-Party Providers (as defined below) in order to support us providing information about user behaviors and Service use and navigation. Further information about the basis upon which we may share such information is set out in this Privacy Policy. We use Nonpersonal Data to help us understand who uses our Service and to improve and market our Service.

**IP Addresses**

In addition to the non Nonpersonal Data highlighted above, we may collect certain information about your computer, including, where available, your IP address or other unique identifiers from your device. This information is collected for system administration (for example to enable identification and log-on for certain services), but also to understand more generally about the way users interact with our Service. In certain cases and in some jurisdictions, these IP addresses may amount to Personal Data or, when used in combination with other data which we hold, may enable us to identify you. This statistical information is not shared [other than with our Affiliates for internal purposes]. Once aggregated, this becomes generic Nonpersonal Data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**Cookies and other Tracking Tools**

We may use certain internet technologies such as “cookies,” “action keys” and “web bugs,” among others (collectively, “ **Tracking Tools** ”). Tracking Tools are files or tools that are placed on your computer in order to identify your Web browser and the activities of your computer on our Service. We do not use Tracking Tools to collect Personal Data other than certain IP addresses which are treated in accordance with this Policy.

When you visit the Service, we may recognize you by a Tracking Tool and customize your use of the Service accordingly (e.g., once you have registered, a cookie will be used to avoid asking you to register again). The information obtained from using these technologies is not sold or otherwise made available to third parties.

The cookies we use are referred to as session or persistent cookies, depending on how long they are used.

Session cookies only last for your online session and disappear from your computer or device when you close your browser.

Persistent cookies stay on your computer or device after the browser has been closed and last for the period of time specified in the cookie. These persistent cookies are activated each time you visit the Property where the cookie was generated.

You can reset your Web browser to refuse certain types of Tracking Tools or to indicate when a Tracking Tool is being sent. However, certain features of the services may not work if you delete or disable Tracking Tools. Additionally, you have the ability to accept or to decline cookies from our Service and other third party Web sites by modifying the settings in your browser. You may, however, not be able to use or access all of the interactive features of the relevant Property if cookies are disabled.

Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Service or certain areas or features of the Service.

For further information on cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION AND WHEN WE MAY SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION GENERALLY**

We use Personal Data for internal purposes only, such as to provide you with the Service, to improve the Service, to fulfill requests for products and services, to notify you of new products or services, and to otherwise communicate with you about I.AM.BIZZY. We may disclose to third parties certain Nonpersonal Data regarding the Service. However, in such cases, your Nonpersonal Data will be aggregated with the Nonpersonal Data of others and will not identify you individually.

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (“ **Third-Party Providers** ”). For example, we may contract with Third-Party Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management and marketing and promotions. We provide our Third-Party Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Third-Party Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

We may provide services jointly with other companies. In some cases, in order to facilitate such services, it may be necessary to share your Personal Data with such other companies. Before we do so, we will identify the partner, present the joint service provider’s privacy policy to you before you use that service, and obtain your permission to share your Personal Data.

We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers and ad networks (" **Advertisers** "). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Site, the Service, or third-party Web sites. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or other Tracking Tool. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you. You can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) Web site, which offers information about Internet advertising companies and how to opt-out of their information collection.

We may share Personal Data and Nonpersonal Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with I.AM.BIZZY. If I.AM.BIZZY is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Data and Nonpersonal data in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our reasonable judgment, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

I.AM.BIZZY cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Data (and any other information about you or content posted or transmitted by you through the Service) to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of I.AM.BIZZY or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

**PROCESSING AND STORAGE OF DATA IN THE UNITED STATES**

Please be aware that your Personal Data and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country.

In particular, if you are based in the European Union, you should be aware that the Personal Data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our Third-Party Providers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of the services you request from us, the processing of your personal details in order for us to provide our services to you and the provision of support services. By submitting your Personal Data, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your Personal Data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that the laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Service you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Data and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

**THIRD-PARTY SERVICES AND APPLICATIONS**

Through the Service, you may elect to access third-party services and applications, such as Facebook and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services. Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Service (e.g., so that you can follow your Facebook friends’ activity). If you elect to enable such third-party services or applications, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings for such services. You also may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications.

**LINKS**

The Service may contain links to Web sites and other interactive services of third parties. We are not responsible for the collection and use of your information by these third parties, which will be governed by their data collection policies. We do not endorse, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices or the content of these other services. Please check these policies before you submit any Personal Data to these Web sites.

**SHARING INFORMATION WITH OTHERS**

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available page or via comments, discussion boards, or any other public forum on the Service, such information may be accessed by others. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, including information in direct messages to other users, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications. We reserve the right to monitor your communications with others conducted through the Service and we may disclose such communications in our discretion for legal enforcement and compliance purposes as described above.

**SECURITY MEASURES**

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Data. Accordingly, we employ reasonable measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure and use. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Service or services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Service and you do so at your own risk.

**CONTACT INFORMATION FOR I.AM.BIZZY RATINGS**

The Data Controller for this Property is i.am.bizzy, llc an entity registered and regulated in the United States of America and located at:

i.am.bizzy, llc c/o Hertz & Lichtenstein, LLP  
450 North Roxbury Drive, 8th Floor  
Beverly Hills, CA 90210

Questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy and data protection practices should be addressed to:  
Webmaster  
i.am.bizzy, llc  
privacy@i.am

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

If you are based in the European Union, your local laws give you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the relevant local legislation. Any access request may be subject to a limited administration fee (up to any limit imposed by local law) to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Property and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. We will endeavor to give you reasonable notice in advance of such changes taking effect, which shall happen on the revision date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Service constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
